Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the President, Kimpton Administration Records 1892-1960
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: General Files
  - Preparation of Teachers, Committee on, minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 202, Folder 15)
  - Presbyterian, St. Luke’s Hospital, 1943-1960 (Box 202, Folder 16)
  - President of the University, Lawrence Alpheus Kimpton, addresses and statements, 1951-1960 (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - President's Fund, 1925-1960 (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - President’s House, Committee on, 1951-1954 (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - President’s and Chancellor’s Reports to Trustees, 1954-1960 (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - President's Report, material for, 1952-1956 (Box 203, Folder 5-6)
  - President's/Chancellor's Seminar, 1955 (Box 203, Folder 7)
  - Primate Research Center, 1960 (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - Princeton University, 1937-1960 (Box 204, Folder 2-4)
  - Printing Department, analysis of factors affecting retention or disposal of the, 1951 (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Prizes, general, 1941-1960 (Box 204, Folder 6-7)
  - Prizes, Undergraduate Teaching, Quantrell Award, 1938-1957 (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - Professors, Distinguished Service, Chancellor’s party for, 1957 (Box 204, Folder 9)
  - Professors, letters about, 1951-1956 (Box 204, Folder 10)
  - Professorships, Distinguished Service and Named, 1956-1959 (Box 204, Folder 11)
  - Professorships, general, Distinguished Service and Named, 1929-1956 (Box 204, Folder 12)
  - Prudential Insurance Company, 1953 (Box 204, Folder 13)
  - Psychiatry, Department of, 1955-1960 (Box 204, Folder 14-15)
  - Psychology, Department of, 1951-1959 (Box 204, Folder 16)
  - Psychology, Department of, 1951-1959 (Box 205, Folder 1-2)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1956-1959 (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, background material, 1934-1954 (Box 205, Folder 4-5)
  - Public Administration Clearing Service, Governing Board, meetings and minutes, 1955-1960 (Box 205, Folder 6-8)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, transfer to Public Administration Clearing Service, 1956-1958 (Box 205, Folder 9)
  - Public Administration Service, financing new wing, 1313 Building, 1944-1959 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Public Affairs Conference Center, 1960 (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - Public Policy Conferences, Committee on, 1959-1960 (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - Public Relations, Office of, 1950-1960 (Box 206, Folder 4-8)
  - Public Relations, Office of, press relations, 1951-1958 (Box 206, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Board of, 1951-1960 (Box 206, Folder 10-13)
  - Publications, Board of, agenda, 1960 (Box 206, Folder 14)
  - Publications, Board of, membership, 1951-1960 (Box 206, Folder 15-16)
  - Publications, Board of, Publications Committees, general, 1942-1955 (Box 206, Folder 17)
  - Publications, minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 207, Folder 1-2)
  - Publications, Office of, proposed, 1956 (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - Publications in Biology and Medicine, Committee on, 1946-1956 (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - Publications in Education, Committee on, 1945-1952 (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - Publications in the Physical Sciences, Committee on, 1946-1956 (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - Pugwash and post-Pugwash meetings, Cyrus S. Eaton, 1955-1959 (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - Purchasing office, 1949-1960 (Box 207, Folder 8-9)
  - Purdue University, 1956-1960 (Box 207, Folder 10)
  - Q, general, 1950-1955 (Box 207, Folder 11)
  - Quadrangle Club, 1914-1960 (Box 207, Folder 12-15)
  - Quadrangle Club, 1952-1959 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Quadrangle Club, annual reports and audits, 1945-1958 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Quadrangle Club, by-laws, 1958-1959 (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - Quadrangle Club, sale of liquor, 1949-1957 (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - Quadrangle Club, subsidy, 1951-1958 (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - Quadrangle Club, survey of operations by Horwath and Horwath, 1954 (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - Race Relations, Institute of, 1952-1956 (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - Racial and religious discrimination, 1954 (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - Radiation Hazards, Committee on, 1946-1959 (Box 208, Folder 9-11)
  - Radiation Hazards, Committee on, 1960 (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - Radiation Hazards, Committee on, membership, 1953-1960 (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Radio, 1948-1957 (Box 209, Folder 3-4)
  - Radio, Board of, membership, 1950-1960 (Box 209, Folder 5-6)
  - Radio, Board of, membership and elimination, 1960 (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - Radio Committees, 1946-1953 (Box 209, Folder 8)
  - Radio, Office of, 1951-1954 (Box 209, Folder 9-10)
  - Radio, Office of, FM, 1944-1953 (Box 209, Folder 11)
  - Radio, Office of, FM, National Association of Educational Broadcasters and Fund for Adult Education Project, 1949-1954 (Box 209, Folder 12)
  - Radio, Office of, history, 1930-1955 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Radio and Television, Office of, 1955-1960 (Box 210, Folder 2-5)
  - Radiology, Department of, 1953-1960 (Box 210, Folder 6-8)
  - Read, Leonard E., 1955-1957 (Box 210, Folder 9)
  - Registrar, Office of, 1951-1960 (Box 210, Folder 10-12)
  - Registrar, Office of, enrollment statistics, veteran enrollment, 1951-1960 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - Reid, Edwin M., suit, 1952-1953 (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Religious activities, 1945-1953 (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - Religious Education Association, 1952-1958 (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Religious survey, 1943-1956 (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Renaissance Society at the University of Chicago, 1955-1960 (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - Reporter Magazine, 1959-1960 (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - "Reports," Research Reports, 1950-1954 (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - Research Center in Economic Development and Cultural Change, 1954-1960 (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - Research Institutes, 1960 (Box 211, Folder 10)
  - Research Institutes, administrative organization, 1949-1953 (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - Research Institutes, annual science open house, 1952-1960 (Box 211, Folder 12)
  - Research Institutes, building, 1951-1959 (Box 211, Folder 13)
  - Research Institutes, Enrico Fermi Institute for Nuclear Studies, 1947-1960 (Box 212, Folder 1-4)
  - Research Institutes, Enrico Fermi Institute for Nuclear Studies, naming of, 1955 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - Research Institutes, general, 1942-1959 (Box 212, Folder 6-7)
  - Research Institutes, Industrial Sponsors, 1945-1955 (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - Research Institutes, industrial sponsors, 1951-1960 (Box 213, Folder 1-4)
  - Research Institutes, Industrial Sponsors Meetings, 1952-1954 (Box 213, Folder 5-7)
  - Research Institutes, Industrial Sponsors Meetings, 1956-1958 (Box 214, Folder 1-6)
  - Research Institutes, Industrial Sponsors Meetings, 1958-1960 (Box 215, Folder 1-7)
  - Research Institutes, Institute of Radiobiology and Biophysics, 1945-1954 (Box 216, Folder 1)
  - Research Institutes, Institute of Radiobiology and Biophysics, Committee on, 1952-1953 (Box 216, Folder 2)
  - Research institutes, James Franck Institute for the Study of Metals, directorship, 1953-1960 (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - Research Institutes, James Franck Institute, materials research laboratory, 1959-1960 (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - Research Institutes, satellite and space probe missions, 1957-1960 (Box 216, Folder 5)
  - Research Institutes, scientific challenge symbolized in the satellites, 1957-1960 (Box 216, Folder 6)
  - Research Institutes, space, 1953-1960 (Box 216, Folder 7)
  - Research reports, 1957-1960 (Box 216, Folder 8)
  - Residential colleges, 1954 (Box 216, Folder 9)
  - Restaurant Administration Center, 1945-1953 (Box 216, Folder 10)
  - Retirement allowances, academic, 1951-1960 (Box 216, Folder 11-13)
  - Retirement Allowances, Committee on Academic, 1942-1959 (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - Retirement allowances, non-academic, 1943-1960 (Box 217, Folder 2-4)
  - Retirement allowances, non-academic, Special Committee on, 1941-1959 (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - Retirement allowances, plans, 1933-1957 (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - Retirement allowances, plans and policies, 1934-1960 (Box 217, Folder 7-8)
  - Retirement Committee, non-academic, 1953-1960 (Box 217, Folder 9)
  - Retirement expenses, academic, 1960 (Box 217, Folder 10)
  - Retirement, faculty members eligible under statutes 18 and 19, 1957 (Box 217, Folder 11)
  - Retirement Fund, proposal to finance faculty at retirement age, 1957 (Box 217, Folder 12)
  - Retirement income plan, non-academic, 1952-1958 (Box 217, Folder 13-14)
  - Retirement income plan, non-academic, 1952-1960 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Retirement plan, faculty, proposal, 1958 (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - Retirement planning and preparation program, evaluation and revision of, 1956 (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - Retirement plans and policies, 1957-1960 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Retirement plans, non-academic, 1951 (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - Retirement Policy, Subcommittee on, 1951 (Box 218, Folder 6)
  - Retirement Policy, Subcommittee on Pensions, 1950-1953 (Box 218, Folder 7)
  - Retirements, non-academic, supplementary allowance and postponed retirements, 1953-1960 (Box 218, Folder 8)
  - R, general, 1950-1955 (Box 218, Folder 9)
  - Robie House, demolition, outside comments, 1957 (Box 218, Folder 10)
  - Robie House, demolition, proposed, clippings, 1957-1958 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Rochester, University of, 1951-1958 (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller Memorial Chapel, 1950-1960 (Box 219, Folder 3-5)
  - Rockefeller Memorial Chapel, broadcasts, 1928-1958 (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller Memorial Chapel, Committee on the Selection and Redefinition of the Deanship, 1956-1960 (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller Memorial Chapel, Deanship, John Beauchamp Thompson, 1948-1958 (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Memorial Chapel, flood lighting, 1954-1955 (Box 219, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller Memorial Chapel, space, choir loft alterations, 1958 (Box 219, Folder 10)
  - Romance Languages and Literatures, Department of, 1951-1960 (Box 219, Folder 11-14)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, centennial, 1956-1958 (Box 219, Folder 15)
  - Roosevelt University, 1945-1952 (Box 219, Folder 16)
  - Rosenberger Medal, 1928-1954 (Box 219, Folder 17)
  - Ross-McElroy Productions, 1960 (Box 219, Folder 18)
  - Rotary Clubs, 1955-1959 (Box 219, Folder 19)
  - ROTC, 1952-1960 (Box 219, Folder 20)
  - Round Table, 1951-1953 (Box 219, Folder 21)
  - Round Table, outside comments on, 1951-1953 (Box 219, Folder 22-23)
  - Round Table, ratings and awards, 1940-1952 (Box 219, Folder 24)
  - Russia, 1955-1960 (Box 220, Folder 1-3)
  - Russian Exchange Program, Inter-University Committee on Travel Grants, 1956-1959 (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - Ryder Fund, proposals of the university, 1957 (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - Ryerson, Edward L., 1941-1955 (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Ryerson, Edward L., portrait, 1957 (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Salaries, data on and information from other schools, etc., 1945-1960 (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - Salaries and other compensations, faculty, 1940-1959 (Box 220, Folder 9-11)
  - Salaries and other compensations, officers and administrators, 1943-1960 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Salary levels, other schools, 1945-1958 (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - Salzburg seminar, 1959-1960 (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Sarah Lawrence College, 1952-1960 (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - Saturday Review, 1958 (Box 221, Folder 5)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, 1938-1960 (Box 221, Folder 6-11)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, American Council of Learned Societies, 1952-1958 (Box 221, Folder 12)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, background data on applications, 1947-1957 (Box 221, Folder 13)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1955-1960 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Chicago historical society fellowships for teachers of history, 1953 (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Coman, Seymour, 1952-1960 (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Fulbright-Hays program, 1951-1960 (Box 222, Folder 4)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Fulbright-Hays program, university recipients of awards, 1953-1960 (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, honor entrance, 1958 (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, individual cases, 1945-1953 (Box 222, Folder 7)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Law School Scholarship Program, 1951-1957 (Box 222, Folder 8)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, University Scholars Program, 1959 (Box 222, Folder 9)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Walgreen, Charles Rudolph, program in American institutions, 1954 (Box 222, Folder 10)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Wilson, Woodrow, national fellowship foundation programs, 1954-1959 (Box 222, Folder 11)
  - Scholarships for Teach Education Program, Interdivisional Committee on, 1960 (Box 222, Folder 12)
  - School and College Program for Teachers, 1953-1954 (Box 222, Folder 13)
  - School and Society, 1959-1960 (Box 222, Folder 14)
  - Science and Industry, Visiting Committee on, 1954-1958 (Box 222, Folder 15)
  - Scientific American, 1948-1959 (Box 222, Folder 16)
  - Scovell, Wellington, and Company, audits, 1957-1959 (Box 222, Folder 17)
  - Scovell, Wellington, and Company, examinations and reports presented to Board of Trustees, 1956-1958 (Box 222, Folder 18)
  - Scrolls, 1956 (Box 222, Folder 19)
  - Secretary, Office of the, budget, 1953-1955 (Box 223, Folder 1-2)
  - Secretary of the Board of Trustees, 1951-1960 (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Security, 1956-1960 (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - Security clearances and regulations, Department of Defense, 1946-1959 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Selection of Departmental Chairmen, Subcommittee on, 1957-1958 (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - Selective Service, deferment requests, 1953-1960 (Box 223, Folder 7)
  - Selective Service, general, 1948-1959 (Box 223, Folder 8)
  - Selective Service and Reservists Bulletins, 1950-1954 (Box 223, Folder 9)
  - Selective Service Scientific Advisory Committee, 1954-1959 (Box 223, Folder 10)
  - Seven universities meetings, 1955-1960 (Box 223, Folder 11-12)
  - S, general, 1950-1955 (Box 223, Folder 13)
  - Shimer College, 1951-1959 (Box 224, Folder 1-4)
  - Shimer College, Joint Trustee-Faculty Committee on Relations with, 1954 (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - Sino-American Conference, June 1960 (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - Slavic Studies, Slavic Area Committee, 1958-1960 (Box 224, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Douglas, Foundation, committee, 1957 (Box 224, Folder 8)
  - Social Science Research Committee, Divisional, 1939-1954 (Box 224, Folder 9)
  - Social Science Research Committee, University, 1945-1959 (Box 224, Folder 10)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, 1951-1960 (Box 224, Folder 11-14)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, 1955-1960 (Box 225, Folder 1-3)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, clippings and comments, 1955-1956 (Box 225, Folder 4)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, Deanship, 1953-1960 (Box 225, Folder 5)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, Divisional Committees, 1940-1954 (Box 225, Folder 6)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, historical outline of development, 1955 (Box 225, Folder 7)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, Social Sciences Research Building, 1929-1954 (Box 225, Folder 8)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, November 10-12, 1955 (Box 225, Folder 9-10)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, papers read, November 10-12, 1955 (Box 225, Folder 11-12)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, papers read, November 10-12, 1955 (Box 226, Folder 1)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, space, 1951-1958 (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, Study of the Need for a New Cyclopedic Treatment of the Social Sciences, final report, August 25, 1955 (Box 226, Folder 3-4)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, 25th Anniversary Celebration, 1955 (Box 226, Folder 5-6)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, visiting committee, 1951-1960 (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - Social Service Administration, School of, 1951-1960 (Box 227, Folder 2-5)
  - Social Service Administration, School of, accreditation, 1953-1959 (Box 227, Folder 6)
  - Social Service Administration, School of, 50th anniversary, 1958-1959 (Box 227, Folder 7)
  - Social Service Administration, School of, space, 1953-1959 (Box 227, Folder 8)
  - Social Service Administration, School of, Training Center for Probation Officers, 1955-1956 (Box 227, Folder 9)
  - Social Service Administration, School of, visiting committee, 1951-1960 (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Social Thought, Committee on, 1951-1960 (Box 228, Folder 2-8)
  - Social Thought, Committee on, background and policies, 1946-1954 (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - Social Thought, Committee on, Committee of Associates, 1955-1960 (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - Social Thought, Committee on, Jacques de Bourbon-Busset visit, April 1957 (Box 229, Folder 3)
  - Social Thought, Committee on, scholarships and fellowships, 1952 (Box 229, Folder 4)
  - Social Thought, Committee on, status of, 1953-1958 (Box 229, Folder 5)
  - Social Thought, Committee on, visits of Marc Chagall to the university, 1956-1958 (Box 229, Folder 6)
  - Society of American Military Engineers, 1956 (Box 229, Folder 7)
  - Sociology, Department of, 1951-1960 (Box 229, Folder 8-11)
  - Sociology, Department of, 1960 (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - South Asia Language and Area Center, 1959-1960 (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - South Asian studies, Committee on, 1958-1960 (Box 230, Folder 3-4)
  - South East Chicago Commission, 1953-1955 (Box 230, Folder 5-6)
  - South East Chicago Commission, 1954-1960 (Box 231, Folder 1-4)
  - South East Chicago Commission, 1956-1958 (Box 232, Folder 1-2)
  - South East Chicago Commission, 1959-1960 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - South East Chicago Commission, annual meetings, 1956-1960 (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - South East Chicago Commission, board of directors, meetings, membership, 1952-1960 (Box 233, Folder 3-4)
  - South East Chicago Commission, clippings, Hyde Park and urban renewal, 1957 (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - South East Chicago Commission, crank letters, 1953-1958 (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - South East Chicago Commission, executive committee meetings, 1952-1960 (Box 234, Folder 1-2)
  - South East Chicago Commission, executive directorship, 1952-1953 (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - South East Chicago Commission, Neighborhood Redevelopment Act, 1953 (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - South East Chicago Commission, south campus plan, 1960 (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - South East Chicago Commission, West Hyde Park, 1957 (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - Southern Association of College and University Business Officers, 1956-1959 (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - Southern Illinois University, 1949-1960 (Box 234, Folder 8-9)
  - Southern Methodist University, 1954-1960 (Box 234, Folder 10)
  - South Side Planning Board, 1951-1958 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Southwest Hyde Park Neighborhood Redevelopment Corporation, 1957-1960 (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - Southwest Hyde Park Redevelopment Corporation, 1955-1956 (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - South West Hyde Park Redevelopment Corporation, 1955-1956 (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - South West Hyde Park Redevelopment Corporation, notices of weekly meetings, 1956-1960 (Box 235, Folder 5)
  - Space, classrooms, 1955-1960 (Box 235, Folder 6)
  - Space needs, 1958-1960 (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - Space studies by outside organizations, proposed, 1959 (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - Space Study, Faculty Committee on, 1958-1960 (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - Speakers Bureau, 1953-1959 (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - Sports Illustrated, 1959-1960 (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University, 1951-1960 (Box 236, Folder 6-10)
  - Stanford University, Daryl H. Pearson, gift information exchange, 1952-1960 (Box 236, Folder 11)
  - State of Illinois, Board of Higher Education, 1959 (Box 236, Folder 12)
  - State Loan Funds for Higher Education, 1957 (Box 236, Folder 13)
  - "State of the University" address, 1939-1959 (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - "State of the University," reports, 1957-1960 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - Statistics, attendance, 1951-1954 (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - Statutes, by-laws, and articles of incorporation, 1955-1958 (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - Statistics, Committee on, post-doctoral awards, 1951-1952 (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - Statistics, Department of, 1956-1960 (Box 237, Folder 6)
  - Statistics, Department of, Chairmanship, 1957-1960 (Box 237, Folder 7)
  - Statistics, enrollment, distribution of candidates for degrees in divisions according to department specialization, 1943-1959 (Box 237, Folder 8-9)
  - Statistics, enrollment, factors affecting, 1950-1959 (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - Statistics, enrollment, maximum, 1946-1956 (Box 238, Folder 2)
  - Statistics, enrollment, news clippings (Box 238, Folder 3)
  - Statistics, enrollment, projections, yearly comparisons, etc., 1935-1959 (Box 238, Folder 4)
  - Statistics, enrollment, report by Raymond Walters, 1944-1960 (Box 238, Folder 5)
  - Statistics, enrollment, trends in institutions of higher education, 1951-1960 (Box 238, Folder 6)
  - Statistics, miscellaneous, 1929-1960 (Box 238, Folder 7-8)
  - Statistics, Netherton study, 1957 (Box 238, Folder 9)
  - Statistics, other schools, 1949-1960 (Box 239, Folder 1-3)
  - Stevenson, Frank F., 1954-1957 (Box 239, Folder 4)
  - Stochastics, 1953-1960 (Box 239, Folder 5)
  - Stritch, His Eminence Samuel Cardinal, 1958 (Box 239, Folder 6)
  - Student aid, 1952-1960 (Box 239, Folder 7-8)
  - Student Council, Chancellor's, 1953-1959 (Box 239, Folder 9)
  - Student Government, charter flights, 1958-1960 (Box 239, Folder 10)
  - Student Government, organizations and activities, 1939-1960 (Box 239, Folder 11-13)
  - Student Government, organizations and activities, 1950-1960 (Box 240, Folder 1-2)
  - Student Interests, Visiting Committee, 1952 (Box 240, Folder 3)
  - Student organizations, WUCB radio station, 1951-1960 (Box 240, Folder 4)
  - Student recruitment, 1951-1960 (Box 240, Folder 5-9)
  - Student Union, 1948-1954 (Box 240, Folder 10)
  - Students-at-large, 1959 (Box 240, Folder 11)
  - Summer faculty colonies, 1957-1959 (Box 240, Folder 12)
  - Summer Quarter, 1950-1960 (Box 240, Folder 13-16)
  - Summer Quarter, teaching costs, 1952-1960 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Surgery, Department of, 1950-1960 (Box 241, Folder 2-5)
  - Swarthmore College, 1959 (Box 241, Folder 6)
  - Sweden, Swedish, 1946-1960 (Box 241, Folder 7)
  - Sweden, Prime Minister of, Tage Hrlander, visit to campus, April 7, 1952 (Box 241, Folder 8)
  - Synchrocyclotron progress reports, 1947-1952 (Box 241, Folder 9)
  - Syracuse University, 1956-1958 (Box 241, Folder 10)
  - Systems, School of, proposal, School of Applied Sciences, 1956-1958 (Box 241, Folder 11)
  - Szilard, Leo, 1945-1959 (Box 241, Folder 12)
  - Tavern Club, 1955-1960 (Box 241, Folder 13)
  - Tax-Exempt Foundations, Cox Committee, 1952 (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - Tax-Exempt Foundations, Reece Committee, 1953-1955 (Box 242, Folder 2)
  - Tax-Exempt Foundations, Reece Committee, hearings, 1954 (Box 242, Folder 3-4)
  - Tax economics of charitable giving, Arthur Anderson and Company, 1959 (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - Taxes, 1951-1960 (Box 243, Folder 2-5)
  - Taxes, proposed changes in federal tax laws affecting endowed institutions, 1933-1959 (Box 243, Folder 6-8)
  - Taxes, taxable status on fellowship and scholarship grants, 1945-1952 (Box 243, Folder 9)
  - Taxes, taxable status on fellowship and scholarship grants, 1946-1954 (Box 244, Folder 1)
  - Teacher Education, 1933-1960 (Box 244, Folder 2)
  - Teacher Education, Center for, 1954-1958 (Box 244, Folder 3)
  - Teacher Education, Council on, 1957-1960 (Box 244, Folder 4)
  - Teacher Education, Council on, membership, 1954-1956 (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - Teacher Education, Council on, minutes, 1954-1960 (Box 244, Folder 6)
  - Teacher Education, Special Committee on Training of Science Teachers in Chicago Public Schools, 1956-1958 (Box 244, Folder 7)
  - Teacher training, 1954-1958 (Box 244, Folder 8)
  - Teachers, University Committee on the Preparation of, 1953 (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Telephone service, 1950-1960 (Box 245, Folder 2-6)
  - Television, Educational, Committee on, 1952-1953 (Box 245, Folder 7)
  - Television, general, 1948-1959 (Box 245, Folder 8-10)